import {Component} from '@angular/core';
import {NgForOf} from '@angular/common';
import {FormsModule} from '@angular/forms';
import {SearchPipe} from './search.pipe';

@Component({
  selector: 'app-root',
  imports: [NgForOf, FormsModule, SearchPipe],
  templateUrl: './app.component.html',
  styleUrls: ['./app.component.css']
})
export class AppComponent {

  questions = [
    {"question": "Which troop type are Calvary (cavalry) strong against?", "answer": " Shieldmen"},
    {"question": "Which troop type are Shieldmen strong against?", "answer": " Spearmen"},
    {"question": "Which troop type are Spearmen strong against ?", "answer": " Cavalry"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is the kingdom trait of Ydvia?", "answer": " Spearmen HP +5%"},
    {"question": "Which troop type is the Falling Log wall fortification strong against?", "answer": " Spearmen"},
    {"question": "Which kind of Dragon Chest can you obtain by defeating a Metallic Fortress in Norheim?", "answer": " Earth"},
    {"question": "Which kind of Dragon Chest can you obtain by defeating a Death Stinger in Norheim?", "answer": " Water"},
    {"question": "By which of the following methods can you earn Dragon Chest?", "answer": "Defeating Gnome Bosses"},
    {"question": "What is the name of the Lightning Dragon ?", "answer": "Taranis"},
    {"question": "What is the name of the Shadow Dragon?", "answer": "Melanthios"},
    {"question": "What is the special effect of the 'Land of Goddesses' Territory Decoration?", "answer": "Reduce troop death rate"},
    {"question": "What is the special effect of the 'Bon Voyage' Territory Decoration?", "answer": "Increase Honor earned from attacking enemies"},
    {"question": "What is the special effect of the 'King of the Supreme' Territory Decoration?", "answer": "Increase territory's Prosperity recovery speed"},
    {"question": "Which of the following can be chosen as the duration of a voyage from the Harbor?", "answer": "All the other answers are correct"},
    {"question": "Which of the following cannot be chosen as the duration of a voyage from a Harbor?", "answer": "1 hour"},
    {"question": "Which of the following cannot be obtained as a reward from trading at the Harbor?", "answer": "Enchant Stone"},
    {"question": "What kind of skill effect is Burn?", "answer": "Continuous damage"},
    {"question": "Which of the following skill effects does not inflict continuous damage?", "answer": "Root"},
    {"question": "Which of the following effects deals continuous physical damage to its target?", "answer": "Judge"},
    {"question": "Which of the following effects deals continuous magical damage to its target?", "answer": "Plague"},
    {"question": "Which of the following skill effects does not redirect damage?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "Which of the following bonuses is gained when you deploy three units of the same element?", "answer": "Immortal Physical Defense +20%"},
    {"question": "Deploying 5 units of the same element grants the following effect: Troop HP +10%.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "How many units of the same element must be deployed for your team to receive a bonus?", "answer": "3"},
    {"question": "By which of the following methods can you obtain Contract Builders?", "answer": "All the other answers are correct"},
    {"question": "Which of the following rewards can be obtained from the Daily Sign-in?", "answer": "All the other answers are correct"},
    {"question": "By which of the following methods can you obtain Enchantment Stones for equipment?", "answer": "Defeating Gnome Units"},
    {"question": "By which of the following methods can you obtain Immortal fragments ?", "answer": "All the other answers are correct"},
    {"question": "Which of the following methods cannot obtain Dragon Crystals?", "answer": "Trading at the Harbor"},
    {"question": "How can the Holy dragon be obtained ?", "answer": "Purchase at the  VIP Points Shop"},
    {"question": "Where can you obtain Immortal upgrade materials?", "answer": "Well of Time"},
    {"question": "What kind of Immortal equipment is dropped after defeating Tyrant Gnomes in Norheim?", "answer": "Weapons and helmets"},
    {"question": "Which of the following actions earns you Alliance Contribution?", "answer": "Alliance Technology donations"},
    {"question": "Which of the following methods cannot earn you Immortal fragments?", "answer": "Attacking other Lords"},
    {"question": "What rewards can you obtain in the Battle of Asteria event?", "answer": "Immortal artifact schematic fragments"},
    {"question": "You can earn Gold resources by praying to the goddess at the Wishing Fountain.", "answer": "Wrong"},
    {"question": "Immortal EXP, used to level up Immortals, can be earned by challenging stage campaigns in the Well of Time.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "In the first three days after the server opens, Alliance members can start the impeachment process if the Alliance Leader does not log in for how many consecutive hours?", "answer": "24 hours"},
    {"question": "Which of the following statements about Immortal attributes is true?", "answer": "Lightning beats Earth"},
    {"question": "Which of the following bonuses are enjoyed by the Scholar of a Castle?", "answer": "Increased building upgrade speed"},
    {"question": "Which of the following bonuses is not enjoyed by the Treasurer of a Castle?", "answer": "Increased gold production speed"},
    {"question": "Which of the following bonuses are enjoyed by the Commander of a Castle?", "answer": "All the other answers are correct"},
    {"question": "How much is Technology research speed increased by when the Academy reaches Lv.40?", "answer": "20%"},
    {"question": "What does the Stellar Crystal item do?", "answer": "Empower artifacts"},
    {"question": "Which of the following requirements must be met to attack a Provincial Capital?", "answer": "Alliance has occupied any city in the relevant province"},
    {"question": "Which of the following Technologies increases the maximum number of cities an Alliance can occupy?", "answer": "Vast Territory"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is not part of the Governor's authority?", "answer": "Bestowing rewards"},
    {"question": "Which of the following actions will cause your territory's Protection status to expire?", "answer": "Attacking other Lords"},
    {"question": "How many levels do Norheim's resource zones come in?", "answer": "5"},
    {"question": "How many provinces are there in Norheim?", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "In the Castle, how many officers can be appointed per official position?", "answer": "3"},
    {"question": "How long does the Bloody Rage status last for?", "answer": "10 minutes"},
    {"question": "How many Ruins Exploration units can a Lord dispatch at the same time?", "answer": "2"},
    {"question": "What is the maximum march distance of a normal relocation?", "answer": "300 km"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is not affected when increasing a Castle's level?", "answer": "Lord level"},
    {"question": "In the Contention of Relics, which of the following conditions must an Alliance meet to crown the king?", "answer": "All the other answers are correct"},
    {"question": "During which round of the Contention of Relics does the World Heart become available to occupy?", "answer": "3"},
    {"question": "What is the massive structure at the very center of Norheim called?", "answer": "World Heart"},
    {"question": "How many consecutive days do you have to log in for to claim a special Lord Avatar Frame?", "answer": "200 days"},
    {"question": "When dismantling Immortal fragments, how many different Immortal fragments can you insert at once?", "answer": "6"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is not a Royal Order?", "answer": "Vast Territory"},
    {"question": "How many occupiable cities are there in Norheim (excluding the Frozen Realm)?", "answer": "87"},
    {"question": "What is the maximum number of Dragon Chests that the Treasury can hold?", "answer": "3"},
    {"question": "Which of the following items can be used to summon Immortals at the Hall of Immortals?", "answer": " Philosopher Stones"},
    {"question": "Missing question: Relocate a territory to another server?", "answer": " Relocate a territory to another server"},
    {"question": "Which of the following Immortals' fragments can be obtained from the Theia's Roulette event ?", "answer": "Theodora"},
    {"question": "What percentage of resources are recovered when dismissing troops?", "answer": "80%"},
    {"question": "What percentage of resources will be returned if you cancel transmuting gold at the Forge?", "answer": "80%"},
    {"question": "How many cities can an Alliance Leader abandon the occupation of per day?", "answer": "3"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is not an effect of reduced Prosperity on territory production?", "answer": "Reduced gold production"},
    {"question": "How much Honor is deducted from Senior Nobility every day?", "answer": "1%"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is not an effect of a blizzard zone in the Legion of Frostborne?", "answer": "Gnomes have reduced strength in battle"},
    {"question": "How many Arena tiers are there?", "answer": "10"},
    {"question": "How many Lord Talents can you equip when dispatching a unit?", "answer": "1"},
    {"question": "What does the Contract Builder item do?", "answer": "Add a temporary building queue for 24 hours"},
    {"question": "At which star grade is an Immortal's first passive skill slot unlocked?", "answer": "3 stars"},
    {"question": "The place where you summon Immortals using Philosophers Stones is called the Hall of Immortals.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "Dwellings in your Territory produce Gold resources.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "The place where you can learn Immortal passive skills is called the Tower of Knowledge", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "Each troop belonging to a Lord is composed of 4 Immortals and 1 dragon.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "You can earn Stone resources by praying to the goddess at the Wishing Fountain.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "An Immortal Fragment of the same name can be used to increase the star level of an Immortal.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "in the Illusion Battlefield, the first Alliance to win how many Violet Breath points wins?", "answer": "100,000"},
    {"question": "In the Illusion Battlefield, how many participating members are allowed per side?", "answer": "40"},
    {"question": "In the Illusion Battlefield, how many Geometric Towers are there?", "answer": "5"},
    {"question": "In the Illusion Battlefield, which of the following is not true?", "answer": "Relocation Cooldown is 10 mins"},
    {"question": "Resource obtained through resource items are secured resources. They will not be stored in your Warehouse and cannot be plundered by other Lords.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "Which of the following statements about gathering resources is false?", "answer": "Units cannot be recalled while they are gathering"},
    {"question": "When resources produced by resource buildings in your Territory reach the storage limit, the workers will stop producing resources.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "Appointing an Immortal as Commander of the Castle can increase soldier training speed and Academy Technology research speed.", "answer": "Wrong"},
    {"question": "What is the maximum number of allied units that can be garrisoned in a territory's wall?", "answer": "4"},
    {"question": "There are a total of 5 types of Wall Fortifications.", "answer": "Wrong"},
    {"question": "The place where you can heal wounded troops is called the Training Grounds.", "answer": "Wrong"},
    {"question": "Bowman Immortals can be deployed in the front row of a unit.", "answer": "Wrong"},
    {"question": "Which of the following levels, when reached, does not cause a Dragon's appearance to change?", "answer": "20"},
    {"question": "How much does the Marching Speedup item increase marching speed by?", "answer": "50%"},
    {"question": "Which of the following methods lets you change your territory's location?", "answer": "All the other answers are correct"},
    {"question": "Which of the following rewards is earned by clearing Stage 5-8 of the Well of Time?", "answer": "Increased building upgrade speed"},
    {"question": "Through which of the following ways can an Alliance Leader publish an Alliance Event?", "answer": "All the other answers are correct"},
    {"question": "Which of the following attributes is reduced when a target is Shackled?", "answer": "Dodge Rate"},
    {"question": "What is the SP cost of challenging a Well of Time stage?", "answer": "10 SP"},
    {"question": "Which of the following actions earns you Honor?", "answer": "Defeating other Lords unit"},
    {"question": "what are the mysterious crystals in the forbidden zone called?", "answer": "Energy Cubes"},
    {"question": "Which Immortal's nickname is 'Legendary Samurai Commander'?", "answer": "Minamoto Yoshitsune"},
    {"question": "Which Immortal's nickname is 'Queen of the Amazon'?", "answer": "Hippolyta"},
    {"question": "Which Immortal's nickname is 'The Great Wizard'?", "answer": "Merlin"},
    {"question": "Which Immortal's nickname is 'William the Conqueror'?", "answer": "William I"},
    {"question": "Which Immortal's nickname is 'Last Samurai'?", "answer": "Sanada Yukimura"},
    {"question": "What is Richards I Nickname Richard I?", "answer": "The Lionheart"},
    {"question": "What is Manco Cápac's nickname Manco Cápac? (capac)", "answer": "The Royal Founder"},
    {"question": "What is Julius Caesar's nickname Julius Caesar?", "answer": "Roman Dictator"},
    {"question": "The Sun's Gift is the exclusive artifact of which Immortal?", "answer": "Ramesses II"},
    {"question": "Titan's Prove is the exclusive artifact of which Immortal?", "answer": "Leonidas"},
    {"question": "What is the name of Hannibal Barca's Hannibal Barca's?", "answer": "The War Colossus"},
    {"question": "What is the name of Hippolyta'sHippolyta's?", "answer": "Godesses' Waist Belt"},
    {"question": "What is Seondeok's Seondeok's?", "answer": " Fire"},
    {"question": "What is Richard I's elemental attribute Richard I's?", "answer": " Lightning"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is not a Shadow Immortal ?", "answer": "Joan of Arc"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is a Wind Immortal ?", "answer": "Qin Emperor"},
    {"question": "What is Hammurabi's ultimate skill Hammurabi's?", "answer": "Final Judgment"},
    {"question": "What is Balwind's ultimate skill? (baldwin)", "answer": "Hurricane"},
    {"question": "Which Immortal's ultimate skill is Shadow Strike?", "answer": "Flavius Belisarius"},
    {"question": "Which Immortal's ultimate skill is Wither Realm?", "answer": "Bjorn"},
    {"question": "What troop type does Cleopatra Lead Cleopatra?", "answer": " Bowman"},
    {"question": "Which troop type does Muhammad II lead?", "answer": " Spearman"},
    {"question": "Which of the following Immortals specializes in leading Shieldmen?", "answer": "Hannibal Barca"},
    {"question": "Which of the following Immortals specializes in leading Cavalry?", "answer": "Siegfried"},
    {"question": "Which of the following Immortal is of the Support class?", "answer": "Dido"},
    {"question": "Who was the only person to defeat Cyrus in major campaign", "answer": "Tomyris"},
    {"question": "What is the emblem of Ruslan?", "answer": "Lion"},
    {"question": "What is the emblem of Vigorous Silvanus?", "answer": "Owl"},
    {"question": "What is the emblem of Vitas?", "answer": "Sacred Tree"},
    {"question": "What was the former capital of the Kingdom of Ruslan?", "answer": "Gallant Vulcan"},
    {"question": "Which city in Norheim was once the capital of Vitas?", "answer": "Vigorous Silvanus"},
    {"question": "Which city in Norheim was once the capital of Ydvia?", "answer": "Dark Minerva"},
    {"question": "What day marks the founding of the kingdom Ruslan?", "answer": "29 Jun"},
    {"question": "What is founding date for kingdom of Vitas", "answer": "14 July"},
    {"question": "What is founding date for kingdom of Ydvia?", "answer": "28 May"},
    {"question": "How many kingdoms coexisted in Norheim before the Empire of Light was founded?", "answer": "5"},
    {"question": "According to the legend of the Ghost Fiesta, what is the name of the girl who drove away the evil goddess Laufey?", "answer": "Laima"},
    {"question": "What holiday do the people of Norheim celebrate in May at the start of summer?", "answer": "Hunting Festival"},
    {"question": "What holiday was mankind celebrating on the day the Gnomes broke past Harold's Ice Wall?", "answer": "Midsummer Festival"},
    {"question": "What is the massive wall of ice in Norheim's north called?", "answer": "Harold's Ice Wall"},
    {"question": "In which year of Norheim's history did the famous War of Allocen begin?", "answer": "1493"},
    {"question": "In which year of Norheim's history was the ruined Sovereign Tomb in the Forbidden Zone rebuilt?", "answer": "1471"},
    {"question": "In which year in Norheim's history was the Royal Alchemist Academy established?", "answer": "1449"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a festival celebrated in Norheim?", "answer": "Sun Festival"},
    {"question": "In which year of Norheim's history did Hornheim create the Gnomes?", "answer": "884"},
    {"question": "Which city is the trade hub of Vitas?", "answer": "Phylria"},
    {"question": "In Greek mythology, who is the daughter of the god of war Ares?", "answer": "Hippolyta"},
    {"question": "In Greek mythology, what was Ares the god of?", "answer": "War"},
    {"question": "In Greek mythology, who was punished to forever roll a boulder up a hill, only for it to roll down again upon reaching the top?", "answer": "Sisyphus"},
    {"question": "In Greek mythology, who stole fire from the gods to give it to humanity?", "answer": "Prometheus"},
    {"question": "In Greek mythology, the Trojan War is said to have been fought over the most beautiful woman in the world. Who is she?", "answer": "Helen"},
    {"question": "In Greek mythology, which hero stole the Golden Fleece?", "answer": "Jason"},
    {"question": "In Greek mythology, what was Achilles' only weak point?", "answer": "Heel"},
    {"question": "What ancient Greek city-state was famous for its harsh military training and strength in warfare?", "answer": "Sparta"},
    {"question": "Where is Olympia located", "answer": "Peloponnese"},
    {"question": "In Greek mythology, who slew Medusa", "answer": "Perseus"},
    {"question": "Plato set up his Academy outside the city walls of Athens. What was the site previously used?", "answer": "Gymnasium"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is the weapon of the Norse god Thor?", "answer": "Mjolnir"},
    {"question": "In Norse Mythology, who keeps the golden apples of eternal youth?", "answer": "Idun"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is the weapon of Frey, the Norse god of fertility?", "answer": "Skidbladnir"},
    {"question": "In Norse mythology, what is the name of the realm of men?", "answer": "Midgard"},
    {"question": "In Norse mythology, what did Loki use to kill Baldr?", "answer": "Mistletoe"},
    {"question": "In Norse mythology, what is the well of wisdom and knowledge called?", "answer": "Mímisbrunnr"},
    {"question": "In Norse mythology, who among the following is not a son of Odin?", "answer": "Loki"},
    {"question": "In Norse Mythology, Gleipnir is the chain that binds Fenrir. Which item was not used to make it?", "answer": "Wings of a bird"},
    {"question": "In Norse Mythology, who will Thor fight during Ragnarok?", "answer": "Jormungandr"},
    {"question": "In Norse Mythology, who will devour Odin during Ragnarok?", "answer": "Fenrir"},
    {"question": "In Norse Mythology, which god is the guardian of the Bifrost", "answer": "Heimdall"},
    {"question": "What did Odin gain when sacrificing his eye?", "answer": "Wisdom"},
    {"question": "Which goddess of Norse mythology was famous for her beautiful golden hair?", "answer": "Sif"},
    {"question": "Of the Ennead in Egyptian mythology, what was Nut the goddess of?", "answer": "Sky"},
    {"question": "Where did the Renaissance first begin?", "answer": "Italy"},
    {"question": "When did the Renaissance begin?", "answer": "Mid-14th century"},
    {"question": "Who among the following was a pioneer of the Renaissance?", "answer": "Dante Alighieri"},
    {"question": "During the Trojan War, who shot Achilles' weak point, killing him?", "answer": "Paris"},
    {"question": "According to Homer's Iliad, how long did the Trojan War last?", "answer": "12 years"},
    {"question": "Where did the Olympic Games originate?", "answer": "Ancient Greece"},
    {"question": "In which year was the ancient Olympic Games first held", "answer": "776 BC"},
    {"question": "The five major events of the Olympic Games were running, long jump, discus, javelin, and which one of the following?", "answer": "Wrestling"},
    {"question": "Which nation was Christopher Columbus from?", "answer": "Italy"},
    {"question": "In which year did Christopher Columbus set foot upon the American continent?", "answer": "1492"},
    {"question": "Which nation was Bartolomeu Dias from?", "answer": "Portugal"},
    {"question": "What did Bartolomeu Dias discover when he voyaged to the southern tip of Africa?", "answer": "Cape of Good Hope"},
    {"question": "What is the longest river in the world?", "answer": "The Nile"},
    {"question": "How many countries does the Amazon River flow through?", "answer": "7"},
    {"question": "What is the longest river in Asia?", "answer": "Yangtze River"},
    {"question": "What is the largest lake in Africa?", "answer": "Lake Victoria"},
    {"question": "What is the deepest lake in the world?", "answer": "Lake Baikal"},
    {"question": "The Caspian Sea is the largest lake on earth.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "On earth, most of Oceania is in the southern hemisphere.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "What is the second longest river in Europe?", "answer": "Danube"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is the tallest peak in Russia?", "answer": "Mount Elbrus"},
    {"question": "What is the largest island in the world?", "answer": "Greenland"},
    {"question": "Where are the largest coral reefs in the world?", "answer": "Australia"},
    {"question": "The Brazilian plateau is in North America.", "answer": "Wrong"},
    {"question": "The Brazilian plateau is the largest plateau on earth.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "Oceans account for about 61% of the earth's surface area.", "answer": "Wrong"},
    {"question": "What is the highest mountain in the world?", "answer": "Mount Everest"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is the second-highest mountain in the world?", "answer": "K2"},
    {"question": "The Andes is the longest mountain range on earth.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "The Amazon rainforest is in South America.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "What is the Strait that famously separates Europe from Asia?", "answer": "Bosporus"},
    {"question": "In Mexico, which day is celebrated as the Day of the Dead?", "answer": "November 2"},
    {"question": "In Japan, which day is celebrated as Respect for the Aged Day?", "answer": "3rd Monday in Sept"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is not part of Dante's Divine Comedy?", "answer": "Earth"},
    {"question": "Who drew the sword in the stone and was hence named king?", "answer": "King Arthur"},
    {"question": "What is the name of the front formed when a cold air mass moves to replace a warm air mass?", "answer": "Cold front"},
    {"question": "Who was the first ever empress of Imperial Russia?", "answer": "Catherine I"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is not a fossil fuel?", "answer": "Nuclear Energy"},
    {"question": "What do frogs use to breathe other than their lungs?", "answer": "Skin"},
    {"question": "Which of the following buildings is not a work of Islamic architecture?", "answer": "Hagia Sophia"},
    {"question": "Which of the following Egyptian landmarks is known as the Sphinx?", "answer": "Great Sphinx of Giza"},
    {"question": "how many bones does adults have?", "answer": "206 bones"},
    {"question": "Who was known as the last pharaoh of the Ptolemaic dynasty?", "answer": "Cleopatra"},
    {"question": "The Baltic states refer to Lithuania, Latvia, and which country?", "answer": "Estonia"},
    {"question": "At the World Swimming Championship, the event with the longest distance is the men's 1500 m in which style?", "answer": "Freestyle"},
    {"question": "In 221 BC, Qin Emperor established the first unified dynasty in Chinese history - the Qin Dynasty.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "In the Southern hemisphere, summer is from June to August, and winter is from December to February.", "answer": "Wrong"},
    {"question": "Ludwig Van Beethoven was born in Bonn, a city in Germany.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "In the solar system, the planet closest to the sun is Venus.", "answer": "Wrong"},
    {"question": "In which year did the British rock band The Beatles disband?", "answer": "1970"},
    {"question": "Osamu Dazai wrote the Japanese work 'No Longer Human'.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is not a work by Shakespeare?", "answer": "A Doll's House"},
    {"question": "Who was the first European to write a detailed account of Chinese history and culture?", "answer": "Marco Polo"},
    {"question": "In 1990, Diego Maradona was named 'Best Player' in the FIFA World Cup.", "answer": "Wrong"},
    {"question": "The 1998 FIFA World Cup was held in France.", "answer": "Correct"},
    {"question": "Who was the only person to have defeated Cyrus the Great in a major campaign?", "answer": "Tomyris"},
    {"question": "In whose honor was the famous Arc de Triomphe in Paris built?", "answer": "Napoleon Bonaparte"},
    {"question": "Which of the following is not a work by Leonardo Da Vinci?", "answer": "Sunflowers"},
    {"question": "Who was first European Mariner to cross the Pacific Ocean?", "answer": "Ferdinand Magellan"},
    {"question": "Who played Captain Jack Sparrow in the movie The Pirates of the Caribbean?", "answer": "Johnny Depp"},
    {"question": "Who wrote The Art of War?", "answer": "Sun Tzu"},
    {"question": "which of the following cannot be done by alliance members", "answer": "Trading Resources"},
    {"question": "Which of the following items can be purchased at the Insignia Shop in the Arena?", "answer": "All the other answers are correct"},
    {"question": "How are targets that are wounded affected?", "answer": "Cannot be healed"},
    {"question": "Which gas makes up 78% of the atmospere? (atmosphere)", "answer": "Nitrogen"},
    {"question": "In which year United States declaration of independence impacted?", "answer": "1776"},
    {"question": "Who was the first European mariner to cross the Pacific Ocean?", "answer": "Ferdinand Magellan"},
    {"question": "Which of these animals cannot stick their tongue out?", "answer": "Crocodile"},
    {"question": "Niagara Falls borders to United states and?", "answer": "Canada"},
    {"question": "Which of the following bodily systems starts to work in a fetus while it is still in the womb?", "answer": "Circulatory"},
    {"question": "Who started the movement that led to the Olympic Games being held once in Athens in 1896, after an interval of 1500 years?", "answer": "Pierre de Coubertin"},
    {"question": "In whose honor was the famous arc de triomphe in Paris built for?", "answer": "Napoleon Bonaparte"}
  ]

  protected filter = '';
}
